Guide to the Goodwin J. (Goodwin Jess) Knight Papers, 1896-1988 (inclusive), 1946-1970 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series 6. Books
  - Subseries 4. Inscribed books
    - California Governors, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 1)
    - Holbrook, James G.: A Survey of Metropolitan Trial Courts - L.A., Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 2)
    - Duffy: State Administrative Machinery for the Conciliation and Mediation of Labor Disputes, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 3)
    - California Youth Authority 1955-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 4)
    - Bench and Bar of Alameda County, California, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 5)
    - Sapoka: Lithuanian Through the Ages, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 6)
    - Goddard: California Landlord-Tenant Law and Procedure, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 7)
    - Roster of Civil and Professional Engineers and Surveyors 1955-6, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 8)
    - Personal Income Tax Law - Bank and Corporation Tax Law 1953,1955, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 9)
    - 11-12. Constitution of the US and California 1951,1957, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 11)
    - 13. Assembly Interim Committee Reports v.22#1 1959-61 Criminal Procedure, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 13)
    - 14. Stanford Convalescent Home 1957, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 14)
    - 15. Roster of Federal State and County and City Officials 1958, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 1)
    - Telephone Directory of State Offices Sacramento 1957, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 16)
    - Freeman: Hesse: A New German State, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 17)
    - Directory of Attorneys 1958, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 18)
    - Assembly Journal Part I 1955, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 19)
    - Governor's Com. on Boxing and Wrestling in Calif. 1956, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 20)
      with note attached: re: phone taps
    - The Pacific Coaster (Metropolitan Life)March 1958, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 21)
    - 100 Years of Masonry 1854-1954, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 22)
    - Proposed Amendments to Constitution General Election 11-7-44, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 23)
    - US Civil Defense1950, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 24)
    - Journal of the Pacific Railway Club v.32#8,9 1948, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 25)
    - Journal of the State Bar of California v.18#2 1943, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 26)
    - Fraternal Order of Eagles 44th annual session 1948, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 27)
    - Science of the Mind October 1954, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 28)
    - Science of the Mind September 1961, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 29)
    - Self-Realization Magazine Sept.-Oct. 1950, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 30)
    - Gillespie's Guide to Los Angeles - City and County, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 31)
    - Premium List State Fair 1957, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 32)
    - Culver City Shrine Club notebook style directory 1949, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 33)
    - Lowell's Poems inscribed (Jess and Lillie Knight Jan. 1909) with inserts, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 34)
    - fragment - cover and title page of The Two Bonanzas by Frank Warner, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 35)
    - Field, Charles K. and Irwin, Will H.: Stanford Stories N.Y. Doubleday 1900 with inseription by Mrs. Leland Stanford to Lula M. Rice (6-4-1900) and ex libris goodwin J. Knight and photo of Jane Stanford., Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 36)
    - Constitution of the US and California 1951,1957, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 12)
    - Personal Income Tax Law - Bank and Corporation Tax Law 1953,1955, Accession no. M0244 (Box 193195, Folder 10)
  - 5. Books from M0245
    This subseries incorporates books from the second accession (M0245) of the Goodwin Knight Papers.
    - McDonald, Emanuel B. "Sam", Sam McDonald's Farm (Stanford: Stanford University Press, 1954)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "To Governor Goodwin J. Knight/my friend of old/With all good wishes/E.B. "Sam" McDonald"
    - Field, Charles K. and Will H. Irwin, Stanford Stories (New York: Doubleday, Page & Co., 1900)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "With/sincere regard to my young friend/Miss Lula M. Rice/from/Mrs. Leland Stanford/June 4th 1900" (with picture)
    - Lewis, Oscar, Here Lived the Californians (New York: Rinehart ~ Co., Inc.,1957)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
    - Eban, Abba, Voice of Israel (New York: Horizon Press, 1957)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "To Governor Goodwin J. Knight/in respect and/friendship/ Abba Eban"
    - Carrillo, Leo, The California I Love (New York: Prentice-Hall, 1961)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "To Goodwin Knight/a valued friend of many years/the life story of our very/dear friend, Leo"
    - Belli, Melvin M,, Dallas Justice (New York: David McKay Co., Inc., 1964)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "To the Honorable/Goodwin J. Knight/with all good wishes/ Melvin Belli/Oct. '64"
    - Reynolds, Quentin, The Amazing Mr. Doolittle (New York: Appleton-Century-Crofts, Inc., 1953)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "To His Excellency/Governor Goodwin J. Knight:/An outstanding public/servant that I have/the pleasure of knowing/ as an intimate and/valued friend./J.H.D."
    - Jones, David W., Forty Years Among thelndians (Salt Lake City: Juvenile Instructor Office, 1890)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "John B. Milner"
    - In Excelsis 17th ed. (New York: The Century Co., 1902)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "Dr. Charles Gardner/to.Goodwin Knight/with the Chaplain's love/Center of the (?)" -- on cover: "Leland Stanford Memorial Church, 1903. Not to be taken away."
    - Bishop, Joseph B. (ed.), Theodore Roosevelt's Letters to his Children (New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1919)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "To My Own Dear/Mother, the first Xmas/we have ever been/apart, and when we/are closer than ever by/her dear letters/from/Goodwin/ Xmas 1919"
    - Knight, Good, Good's Budget (San Diego: Frye & Smith, 1910)., Accession no. M0245; (2 copies - second in poorer condition and not inscribed) (Box 104)
      "Mrs. L. J. Knight/9l9 So. New Hampshire/Los Angeles/Cal."
    - Reps, Paul, Exploring Our Name (Montrose, Ca.: Preview Publications, 1938)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "To Goodwin J. Knight/an understanding friend/Paul Reps"
    - Walsh,Christy, Adios to Ghosts (privately printed?, 1937)., Accession no. M0245; "for (Box 104)
      Judge Knight/with my kindest/regards always/Christy Walsh" Chessman,
    - Caryl, Cell 2455 Death Row (New York: Prentice-Hall Inc., 1954)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 104)
      "For/Governor Goodwin J. Knight/Morituri te Chessman"salutamus!/ Caryl
    - Golden Gate Bridge and Highway District, The Golden Gate Bridge(San Francisco, Jan. 1938). #3878, Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "To Governor Goodwin J. Knight/Compliments Bridge and Highway District/San of/James Adam/General Manager/ Golden Gate Francisco/October 26,1954"
    - Martindale, Emory D., American Concepts and Standards (LA: Wm. B. Straube, ?)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "To Goodwin J. Knight, Esq./Presented with the/author./Ernory D.the/compliments of Martindale"
    - Beek, Joseph A., The California Legislature (Sacramento: Cal. St. Ptg. Office, 1950)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "Goodwin 3. Knight"
    - Padilla, Ambrosio, Public Addresses (Manila: G. Rangel ~ Sons, 1958)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "Governor and Mrs. Goodwin J. Knight/this pamphlet is sincerely presented/Ambrosio Padillo/Manila/Mar. 18. 1958"
    - Mann, Carl, Lightning in the Sky (New York: Robert M. McBride Co., 1943)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "Dr. Israel H. Doolittle/South Bend, Indiana/ To Goodie and Virginia:/ With respect, admiration and/affection. /Jim Doolittle"
    - Melendy, H. Brett and Benjamin F. Gilbert, The Governors of California(Georgetown, Ca.: The Talisman Press, 1965)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
    - Rogers, C.M., Famous Men's Letters to Youth (San Leandro: Service Press, 1955)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
    - Beebe, Lucius and Charles Clegg, Legends of the Comstock Lode (Stanford: Stanford Univ. Press, 1956. 5th ed.), Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "For Gov'r and Mrs./Goodwin Knight/with all good will/From/Lucius Beebe/Virginia City/l957"
    - Scott, Hugh D., Jr., How to Go Into Politics (New York: The John Day, 1949)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "To 'Boswell' Knight/from one who admires/him as a man and/ for the sturdy vigor of/his Republicanism--/His friend./Hugh D. Scott Jr."
    - Roney, Don H., The California Citizen (Houston: Elsevier Press, Inc., 1955)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "Knight"
    - Gilmour, Rev. R., Bible History (New York: Benziger Bros., 1904)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
    - Garland, Hamlin, Trail-Makers ofthe Middle Border (New York: MacMillan Co., 1926)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "Inscribed, at request/of Vidu Sutton To/Mr. Jesse Knight/by the writer/Hamlin Garland/Mr. 29/1926"
    - Bolton, H. E., ThePadreon Horseback (San Francisco: Sonora Press, 1932)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
    - Van Dyke, Henry, The Lost Boy (New York: Harper ~ Bros., 1914)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "To Arvilla/from Mary/Christmas 1919/Ogden, Utah"
    - Spellman, Francis J., NoGreater Love (New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1946)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "Governor/Goodwin J. Knight,/with best wishes and/kindest regards/Cardinal Spellman/October 22, 1955"
    - Spellman, Franàis Cardinal, What America Means to Me (New York: Charles Scribner's Sons, 1953)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "Governor Goodwin Knight/with esteem/and in friendship/F. Card'l. Spellman"
    - Anderson, John F., An Endeavorer's Working Journey Around the World (St. Louis:Christian Publishing Co., 1903)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 105)
      "John Fisher Anderson"
    - Fischer, Martin (transl.), A Truthtelling Manual and the Art of Wordly Wisdom (Springfield: Charles C. Thomas, 1945)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
      "To/Goodwin/Gracian' s/gems added to/those which already/sparkle in your/mind... /Merry Xmas ~/Virginia/1953"
    - Markham, Edwin, The Man with the Hoe and Other Poems (Garden City: Doubleday, Page e~ Co., 1913)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
      "Edwin Markham/August l9l5/C.Telford Work/Venice/Cal ./8/22/l5"
    - The Holy Bible (King James ed.) (Cleveland: The World Publ. Co., ND), Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
      "Dear Goodwin/'Religion secures for us/that which we most/desire, if we do what/it most requires'/Dickinson Miller/Each day our prayer/ will be made that/God's richest blessings/may be yours./ John Christfield Donnell/October 5, 1953" (with inserts)
    - Gibran, Kahlil, The Prophet (New York: Alfred Knopf, 1960)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
      "To Goodwin J. Knight/Here are some lovely/thoughts for a/great American,/a great Californian,/a great'guy' -/Brad Frenham/Cinco de Mayo 1961"
    - Delmatier,TheRumble of California Politics 1848-1970, Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
    - Hill, Gladwin, Dancing Bear, Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
    - Phillips, H.L., Big Wayward Girl, Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
    - Druxnmond, Henry, TheGreatest Thing in the World ('London;Collins, ND)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
      "To Governor/Goodwin J. Knight/3-30-49/Nelson B. Hininan"
    - Hagedorn, Hermann, The Roosevelt Family of Sagamore Hill (New York: MacMillan, 1954)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
      "Inscribed for Governor Goodwin K. (sic) With best wishes -/Hermann Hagedorn/1955."Knight/who is administering the government of/California with the spirit of TR to/guide him./
    - Chapel, Charles Edward, Guns of the Old West (New York: Coward McCann, 1961)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
      "To:/Goodwin J. Knight/with the best regards of%Charles Edward Chapel/ 'Charlie"
    - The Presidents, Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
    - Bolles, Albert S., Home Library of Law Business Man's LegalAdvisor v.3 & 6 Doubleday- Review of Reviews Co. 1912)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
      "G.J. Knight/919 So. N.H."
    - Cutler, Leland W., Once Upon a Time (San Francisco: John Henry Nash, 1934)., Accession no. M0245 (Box 106)
- Series 7. Audiovisual materials
  Records, tape recordings and films comprise the audio-visual series. Some of these materials have been viewed, but not all of them, as proper equipment was unavailable for some of the films.
  The Media materials require at least two weeks advance notice to use in order to allow staff time to have use copies made from the original items.
  - Subseries 1. Sound discs
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with:Sam Collins(3 records), Accession no. M0244 (Box 174, Folder 1)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: Harold Levering, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 2)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: Sen. H.J. Powers, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 3)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: Paul Mason, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 4)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: Sen. Nelson Dilworth, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 5)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: Mrs. K. T. Niehouse, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 6)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: J. B. Cook and Pat McGee of Assembly, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 7)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: Sen. H. T. Parkman, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 8)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: E. R. Geddes of Assembly, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 9)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: C. W. Lyons of Assembly, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 10)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: Arthur Corey and Robert McKay, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 11)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight for Farmer's Insurance with: Sen. James McBride, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 12)
    - 1951 A Civic Tribute to Joseph Scott, Accession no. M0244; (7 records) (Box 174, Folder 13)
    - 1955 (6-28records) Rufus B. vonKleinSmid Dinner, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 14)
    - 1948 Grand Circuit Meeting (Santa Anitarecords), Accession no. M0244; (1 records) (Box 174, Folder 15)
    - 1966 (3-17records) Friendly Sons of St. Patrick, Accession no. M0244; (1 records) (Box 174, Folder 16)
    - 1948 (10-8records) Los Angeles Rotary Club, Accession no. M0244; (3 records) (Box 174, Folder 17)
    - Politics USA, Accession no. M0244; (1 records) (Box 174, Folder 18)
    - Big News of '57, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 174, Folder 19)
    - Natl. Rep. Club (Ike for 4 More Yrs./God Bless America records), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Battle Hymn/To You and Your Lady, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 2)
    - Knight on Abraham Lincoln, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Personal Message from GJK, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Americans, We're All Americans, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Challenge Ahead5-4-54, Accession no. M0244; (4 records) (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Lt. Gov. (dubbed records) I: H.G. Wells (Reno records) KOLO, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Lt. Gov. (dubbed records) II: H.G. Wells (Reno records) KOLO, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - 1946 Santa Anita Handicap (Carolyn Knight records), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Let's Go to Church program, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Swearing-In Ceremonies, Gov. GJK10-5-53, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - copy 2 of above, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 12)
    - Knox Manning KROY4-15-47, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 13)
    - America's Town Meeting 1-29-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 14)
    - Talks to the People KOVR10-31-55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 15)
    - Talks to the People KOVR11-28-55, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 16)
    - Governor's Report12-26-55, Accession no. M0244; KOVR (Box 175, Folder 17)
    - Employment Bldg. Cornerstone9-28-55, Accession no. M0244; Sacto. (Box 175, Folder 18)
    - Capitol Company Unit Dedication, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 19)
    - Interview with Lt. Gov. and HG Wells KOZO, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 20)
    - Lt. Gov. General speech, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 21)
    - Lt. Gov. 11th Anniversary AFRS (Radio Services records), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 22)
    - Lt. Gov. 12-18-47, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 23)
    - KXOC Red Bluff Diversion Dam10-17-53, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 24)
    - Governor Salutes Israel 10th Anniversary, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 25)
    - Western Safety Conference1948 (June 16), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 26)
    - Goodwin Knight Round Table 1956, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 27)
    - Martha Deane Show 4-9-56, Accession no. M0244; WOR (3 records) (Box 175, Folder 28)
    - Knight portion of Warning Bell CBS KROY, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 29)
    - Knight-Mozley Interview re: GOP Conv. 7-24-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 30)
    - Knight Interview2-20-57, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 31)
    - State Fair KLX Oakland, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 32)
    - Sonata #1 Schubert (Hague records), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 33)
    - Meet the Press10-23-55, Accession no. M0244; (3 records) (Box 175, Folder 34)
    - Robt. E. Burns Anniv. Address2-25-57, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 35)
    - Gov.'s Conf. on Education 10-1-55, Accession no. M0244; and choir (Box 175, Folder 36)
    - A Blind Man Looks at You (J. Garfield records) tape also, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 37)
    - Christmas Party for the Blind (Garfield records) 1955, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 38)
    - Pasadena (? records), Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 39)
    - California Caravan6-4-50, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 40)
    - Open Forum (glass base - fragile records), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 41)
    - Our Goodie 5-6-54, Accession no. M0244; (Miss Reynolds records) (Box 175, Folder 42)
    - Veterans Bldg. Napa w/Mrs. K. 2-11-57, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 43)
    - Marin Arts and Garden Center, Accession no. M0244; (3 records) (Box 175, Folder 44)
    - same as above, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 456)
    - KENL Arcata-Eureka3-21-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 47)
    - Presidential Primary, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 48)
    - National Radio Week KROY, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 49)
    - Immigration and Citizenship Dinner 4-9-?, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 50)
    - Paradise Dam Dedication12-9-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 51)
    - Charles Coughlin Interview10-5-53, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 52)
    - Marjorie King Show9-28-56, Accession no. M0244; (SF records) (Box 175, Folder 53)
    - Help Wanted9-26-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 54)
    - Ladies' Coffee Hour 4-15-54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 55)
      California's Future and You
    - VIP Program Freeman Lusk 10-1-53, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 56)
    - Salvation Army(Christmas 1956), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 57)
    - Virginia Carlson10-29-45, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 58)
    - Salvation Army(Christmas 1955), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 59)
    - Corinne Griffith Interview6-7-54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 60)
    - California's Long White Potatoes5-26-55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 61)
    - Los Alamitos Inspection (Gov. K.), Accession no. M0244; (4 records) (Box 175, Folder 62)
    - Lt. Gov. Knight12-18-47, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 63)
    - Unidentified, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 64)
    - Hi-Fi Test12-2-55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 65)
    - Sacramento Festival w/Geo. Murphy5-29-55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 66)
    - Personnel Bldg. Dedication4-1-55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 67)
    - Govs. Knight and Miner and Westinghouse Program1956, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 68)
    - The Smog Song Wm. O. HicksDec. 1954, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 69)
    - Address to Legislature(3-5-56), Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 70)
    - USF Centennial Ballet2-1-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 71)
    - Cavalcade of Books KNXT-TV4-15-56, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 72)
    - (6 records) unidentified, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 73)
    - (2 records) unidentified from William Ladd (employment? records), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 74)
    - (1 records) unidentified, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 75)
    - Gov. Knight Recordio Discs, Accession no. M0244; (2 records) (Box 175, Folder 76)
    - Goodwin Knight Victory March, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 77)
    - Goodwin Knight for Governor, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 78)
    - Gov. Knight speech, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 79)
    - America You're In My Heart M G Sherwood6-54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 80)
    - Audograph Report to the People2-8-54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 81)
    - Audograph Budget Message3-1-54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 82)
    - Open Forum demo rec (damaged) medium, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 83)
    - Open Forum demo rec regular, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 84)
    - 1 album (5) KNX radio Minority Report, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 85)
    - 8-12-55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 1)
    - 1-7-54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 2)
    - 6-27-43(2 records), Accession no. M0244 (Box 3)
    - 7-4-43(2 records), Accession no. M0244 (Box 4)
    - ABC Report on Rep. Natl. Conv.1956 (8-20), Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 86)
    - ABC8-20-56, Accession no. M0244 (Box 175, Folder 87)
      Mrs. GJK and Paul Harvey
    - This is LA General MacArthur Ceremonies, Accession no. M0244; (3 Records) (Box 175, Folder 88)
  - Subseries 2. Audiotapes
    - Rotary Club - Berkeley Hotel Shattuck3-9-55, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 1)
    - Feather River Speech KXOC Chico, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Conference on Water, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 3)
    - James (Wm. F.) Boys' Ranch Program (Rerun), Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 4)
    - Firing Line I, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 5)
    - Firing Line II, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - State Capitol Meeting I Bob Alderman, GJK, and Paul?, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - same as above, part II1-18-54, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Lincoln Day Address 2-11-61, Accession no. M0244; Kern Co. R. C. Bakersfield (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Governor Knight Round Table, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    - Bob Grant KABC8-5-65, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Grant Nite Line8-5-65, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Fishman-Brown Interview Oct. 1960, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Capitol Rotunda Christmas Festival, Accession no. M0244 (Box 176, Folder 14)